Lowell Thomas Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 2. Phonograph records, 1930 - 1955; 2; Boxes: 1819 - 1839
  - Subseries 2.2: For use in the "The Ice Men" production, 2.2; Box: 1820
    - Columbia (17 Ice), undated (Folder 71.12, Box 1820)
      Xavier Cugat and his Orchestra S1: Miami Beach Rhumba Rhumba- Vocal Chorus by Aladdin and The Boyd Triplets -Gamse-Fields- S2: Come to Mardi Gras (Nao Tenho Lagrimas) Samba - Vocal Chorus by Aladdin and The Boyd Triplets -Drake-Shirl-Bulhoes-de Oliveira-
    - Columbia (43 Ice), undated (Folder 71.13, Box 1820)
      Boris Godounov Leopold Stokowski conducting the All-American Orchestra S1: Symphonic Synthesis (Part I) S2: Symphonic Synthesis (Part IV) -Moussorgsky-Stokowski-
    - Columbia (23 Ice Finale, R.I), undated (Folder 71.14, Box 1820)
      Symphony No.2 in D Major -Sibelius, Op. 43- The Philharmonic-Symphony Orchestra of New York John Barbirolli, Conductor S1: Second Movement: Andante (conclusion) S2: Third Movement: Vivacissimo (Beginning)
    - (31 Ice), undated (Folder 71.15, Box 1820)
      Sepp Mollinger Side 2 Taped off
    - Columbia (24/ Open R-2 Ice), undated (Folder 71.16, Box 1820)
      Ibert Escales (Ports of Call) The Philharmonic-Symphony Orchestra of New York Artur Rodzinski, Conductor
    - (15 Ice) and (137), undated (Folder 71.17, Box 1820)
      S1: Woman Screaming (5 cuts) S2: Crowd Effects 1. Screams of terror, mixed 2. Boos, mixed
    - Continental, undated (Folder 71.18, Box 1820)
      Maloof Oriental Orchestra (A. Maloof) S1: Trip to Syria S2: Fatima
    - Sound Effects (10 Ice) and (Brakes), undated (Folder 71.19, Box 1820)
      S1: Explosions (4 cuts) 1. Three heavy explosions 2. One heavy explosion 3. One heavy explosion 4. Series of explosions S2: Air Hammers and Tire Skids (3 cuts) 1. Air hammers - compressor in background 2. Single Air hammer (cont.) 3. Tire skid (cont.)
    - CBS No.5 Sound Effects 375 (12/35 Ice), undated (Folder 71.20, Box 1820)
      S1: Four Engine Landings (3 cuts) 1. Plane fades in, wheels touch, taxis and stops 2. Same as above, different plane 3. Long fade in, wheels touch, fade out S2: Four Engine Airplane (2 cuts) 1. Engines idling 2. Idling, spiral, idles for 8 seconds, spiral, take-off and fade
    - Sound Effects (332) and (332 x2) and (46), undated (Folder 71.21, Box 1820)
      S1: Planes (1) Twin Engine Plane - One Engine Missing (2) Fast Bomber Plane Dives and Zooms for Altitude (3) Squadron of Planes Passing S2: (1) Plane Stunting (2) Squadron of Planes Passing
    - Sound Effects (313) (9/36 Ice) and (313), undated (Folder 71.22, Box 1820)
      S1: Airplanes 1. Power Dive and Crash 2. Take Off - Training Plane 3. Take Off - D-2 Transport 3. Take Off - Kinner Single Motor S2: Crowd Effect Very small group, polite conversation, Typical drawing room
    - Sound Effects (6/40 Ice) and (321), undated (Folder 71.23, Box 1820)
      S1: Airplane Effects (2 cuts) 1. Inertia starter, engines on, plane taxis up field, takes off past microphone, fades 2. Landing at airport, taxis to microphone, kills motors (Douglas D-2 Transport) S2: Airplane Effects (4 cuts) 1. Single motor pursuit ship - power dive - fade 2. Single motor pursuit ship - barrel roll - fade 3. Plane falling - dead motor, wire whine - steady 4. Douglas D-2 transport - motors idling
    - CBS No. 2 Sound Effects (380) and (3) (16/47 Ice), undated (Folder 71.24, Box 1820)
      Fast Aircraft (Jet)
    - CBS No. 31 Sound Effects (912) and (21/26 Ice), undated (Folder 71.25, Box 1820)
      S1: Zooming plane with sound of wind whistling thru struts and crash S2: Various Boat Whistles
    - CBS Sound Effects (923) and (30 Ice), undated (Folder 71.26, Box 1820)
      S1: (1) Country Fire Alarm (2-3-4) Klaxon Horn (5) Klaxon Horn (6) Burglar Alarm Bell (7) Burglar Alarm Bell (8) Siren (prison type) S2: (1) Drum Corp (2-3-4) Trapeze Effect - drum roll and cymbal crash (5) Cymbal Roll and Crash (6) Execution drum and volley of rifles
    - Sound Effects (105) and (25 Ice), undated (Folder 71.27, Box 1820)
      S1: Baby Crying (continuous) S2: Screams - Snores- Typewriters
    - CBS No. 25 Sound Effects (769) and (32 Ice), undated (Folder 71.28, Box 1820)
      S1: Compressor and Pump Effects (2 cuts) 1. Air compressor and motor in continuous operation; occasional sound of air escaping from safety valve 2. Bilge pump, hand operated in small boat S2: Air Hammers, Tire Skid (3 cuts) 1. Air hammers, generator in background 2. Single air hammer, continuous 3. Tire skid, continuous
    - Columbia (27 Ice) and (88)[?], undated (Folder 71.29, Box 1820)
      Gaite Parisienne Efrem Kurtz conducting The London Philharmonic Orchestra S1: 1. Gallop 2. Valse 3. March S2: 1. Grande Valse 2. Finale: Can Can No. 1 -Offenbach- Arraigned: Rosenthal
    - RCA Victor (Ice 5) and (No X), undated (Folder 71.30, Box 1820)
      Rimsky-Korsakov Scheherazade-Symphonic Suite, Op. 35 San Francisco Symphony Orchestra Pierre Monteux Conducting S1: II. The Tale of the Prince Kalender (part 1) S2: III. The Young Prince and the Young Princess (concluded)
    - CBS No. 2 Sound Effects (1051) and (19 Ice), undated (Folder 71.31, Box 1820)
      Sound Effects (Boing) [Boeing?] CBS 2/26/51 SFX 1030 Part 1 and Part 2
    - Columbia (14 Ice), undated (Folder 71.32, Box 1820)
      Beethoven Symphony No. 2 in D Major, Op. 36 Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra Fritz Reiner, Conductor
    - Lowell Thomas (8/Hold Ice), undated (Folder 71.33, Box 1820)
      KCBS Line Check 5/5/52
    - RCA Victor (33), undated (Folder 71.34, Box 1820)
    - Sound Effects (18 Ice) and (915), undated (Folder 71.35, Box 1820)
      S1: Bells No. 3 (3 cuts) (1) Two church bells ringing (2) One church bell ringing (3) One church bell ringing three strokes S2: Bells No. 4 ( 2 cuts) One church bell ringing
    - RCA Victor (1 Ice), undated (Folder 71.36, Box 1820)
    - Columbia (5a), undated (Folder 71.37, Box 1820)
      Khachaturian Gayne - Ballet Suite Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra of New York Conducted by Efrem Kurtz S1: Sabre Dance S2: Lezqhinka
    - RCA Victor (1/5 Ice), undated (Folder 71.38, Box 1820)
    - Columbia (22 [?]), undated (Folder 71.39, Box 1820)
      Boris Godounov Leopold Stokowski conducting the All-American Orchestra S1: Symphonic Synthesis (Part III) S2: Symphonic Synthesis (Part IV) -Moussorgsky-Stokowski-
    - Columbia (Ice Finale), undated (Folder 71.40, Box 1820)
      The Cleveland Orchestra Artur Rodzinski, Conductor Overture 1812 -Tchaikovsky- Parts 3 and [?]
    - Bell Records (42 Ice), undated (Folder 71.41, Box 1820)
      Bill Aliiloa Lincoln and his Hawaiians S1: “Honaunau Paka” (Rose Peters) S2: My Lovely Hawaiian Maid (Esther K. Smith)
  - Subseries 2.3: For use in untitled production, 2.3; Box: 1821
    - Decca (S s.t.), undated (Folder 73.01, Box 1821)
      Jimmy Dorsey and his Orchestra S1: I Love To Watch the Moonlight (Josef Myrow-Bickley Reichner) S2: I Can’t Resist You (Will Donaldson-Ned Wever)
    - Bluebird (S s.t.), undated (Folder 73.02, Box 1821)
      Glen Miller and his Orchestra S1: Faithful Forever (Leo Robin-Ralph Rainger) Vocal refrain by Ray Eberle S2: Bluebirds in the Moonlight (Leo Robin-Ralph Rainger) Vocal refrain by Marion Hutton
    - Bluebird (S s.t.), undated (Folder 73.03, Box 1821)
      Glen Miller and his Orchestra S1: Stairway to the Stars (Parish-Malneck-Signorelli) Vocal refrain by Ray Eberle S2: To You (Dorsey-Shapiro-Davis) Vocal refrain by Ray Eberle
    - Victor (S s.t.), undated (Folder 73.04, Box 1821)
      Tommy Dorsey and his Orchestra S1: To You (Dorsey-Shapiro-Davis) Vocal refrain by Jack Leonard S2:This is No Dream (Ted Shapiro-Benny Davis) Vocal refrain by Jack Leonard
    - Bluebird (S s.t.), undated (Folder 73.05, Box 1821)
      Glenn Miller and his Orchestra S1: In an Old Dutch Garden (Mack Gordon-Will Grosz) Vocal refrain by Ray Eberle S2: Starlit Hour (Mitchell Parish-Peter DeRose) Vocal refrain by Ray Eberle
    - Victor (s.t.) and (F s.t.), undated (Folder 73.06, Box 1821)
      Tommy Dorsey and his Orchestra S1: Hold Tight - Hold Tight (Kent Brandow-Robinson Ware Spotswood) S2: Symphony in Riffs (Benny Carter-Irving Mills)
    - Bluebird (F s.t.), undated (Folder 73.07, Box 1821)
      Artie Shaw and his Orchestra S1: Traffic Jam (Teddy McCrae-Artie Shaw) S2: Serenade to a Savage (Joe Garland-Edgar Battle)
    - Brunswick (s.t.) and (F s.t.), undated (Folder 73.08, Box 1821)
      Harry James and his Orchestra S1: ‘Tain’t What You Do -Oliver-Young- S2: Two O’Clock Jump -Harry James-
    - Vocalion (F s.t.), undated (Folder 73.09, Box 1821)
      Cab Calloway and his Orchestra S1: Trylon Swing -Mills-Bostic S2: The Jumpin’ Jive -Calloway-Froeba-Palmer-
    - Bluebird (M s.t.), undated (Folder 73.10, Box 1821)
      Charlie Barnet and his Orchestra S1: For Tonight (Gannon-Mann-Weiss) Vocal refrain by Larry Taylor S2: What’s New? (Bob Haggart-Johnny Burke) Vocal refrain by Larry Taylor
    - Bluebird (M s.t.), undated (Folder 73.11, Box 1821)
      Glenn Miller and his Orchestra S1: Faithful to You (Block-Green-Stoner) Vocal refrain by Ray Eberle S2:It’s a Blue World (Bob Wright-Chet Forrest)
    - Victor (s.t.) and (M s.t.), undated (Folder 73.12, Box 1821)
      Benny Goodman and his Orchestra S1: Bach Goes to Town (Alec Templeton) S2: Whispering (M. & J. Schonberger-arrainged by Fletcher Henderson
    - Bluebird (M s.t.), undated (Folder 73.13, Box 1821)
      Artie Shaw and his Orchestra S1: Moonray (Shaw-Madison-Quenzer) S2: Melancholy Mood (Vic Knight-Walt Schrmann)
    - Victor (M s.t.) and (s.t.), undated (Folder 73.14, Box 1821)
      Benny Goodman and his Orchestra S1: And the Angels Sing (Johnny Mercer-Ziggie Elman) Vocal Refrain by Martha Tilton S2: Sent For You Yesturday and Here You Come Today (Rushing-Durham-Basie) Vocal Refrain by Johnny Mercer
    - Victor (Sonny Skiing), undated (Folder 73.15, Box 1821)
      Glahe Musette Orchestra S1: Hot Pretzels S2: Beer Barrel
    - Blurbird (good), undated (Folder 73.16, Box 1821)
      Glenn Miller and his Orchestra S1: Sunrise Serenade (Frankie Carle) S2: Moonlight Serenade (Glenn Miller)
    - Victor (ok run it on Medium), undated (Folder 73.17, Box 1821)
      Xavier Cugat and his Waldorf-Astoria Orchestra S1: Night Must Fall (Xavier Cugat) S1: Cui Cui (Faustino Curvelo-X. Cugat) Vocal refrain by Catalino Rolon and Chorus
    - Victor (F9), undated (Folder 73.18, Box 1821)
      Pietro S1: El Choclo (A. G. Villoldo-arrainged Pietro) Accordion Trio S1: Beautiful Days (Pietro) Accordion Duet
    - Victor (I 10), undated (Folder 73.19, Box 1821)
      Chris Chapman with Orchestra Dill Pickles Rag (Johnson)
  - Subseries 2.4: Personal record collection, 2.4; Boxes: 1822 - 1825
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 72.01, Box 1822)
      Meistersinger: Prelude S1: Beginning S2: Conclusion -Wagner- Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra Fritz Reiner, Conductor
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 72.02, Box 1822)
      Egmont Overture In 2 Parts (Beethoven, Op. 84) Felix Weingartner conducting the Vienna Philharmonic Orchestra
    - Victor, undated (Folder 72.03, Box 1822)
      Boston “Pops” Orchestra Arthur Fiedler, Conductor S1: Morning, Noon and Night in Vienna - Overture S2: Light Cavalry - Overture (Part 1) (Von Suppe)
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 72.04, Box 1822)
      Invitation to the Dance -Weber, Op. 65 - Stokowski- Leopold Stokowski conducting The All - American Orchestra
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 72.05, Box 1822)
      Chas. R. Rogers Production “Delightfully Dangerous” S1: “I’m only Teasin’” Sung by Connie Moore Morton Gould & Orchestra S2: “Thru Your Eyes To Your Heart” Sung by Jane Powell Morton Gould & Orchestra
    - Vienna: City of Dreams, 1963 (Folder 72.06, Box 1822)
      The Zither Magic of Anton Karas Featuring the 3rd Man Theme
    - Victor, undated (Folder 72.07, Box 1822)
      Finlandia (Symphonic Poem) (Sibelius), Op. 26, No.7) The Philadelphia Orchestra Eugene Ormandy, Conductor Part 1 and “concluded”
    - Rachmaninoff Concerto No. 2, undated (Folder 72.08, Box 1822)
      Rachmaninoff Concerto No. 2 in C minor, op. 18 Pianist Arthur Rubinstein NBC Symphony Orchestra Vladimir Golschmann conducting
    - Golden March Favorites, undated (Folder 72.09, Box 1822)
      The Goldman Band Under the Direction of Edwin Franko (founder) and Richard Franko Goldman 1. Stars and Stripes Forever 2. El Capitan 3. Washington Post 4. National Emblem March 5. High School Cadets 6. King Cotton 7. Semper Fidelis 8. Colonel Bogey March 9. On the Mall 10. The Marines’ Hymn 11. Dixie 12. The Thunderer
    - It’s Halftime U.S.A, 1964 (Folder 72.10, Box 1822)
      It’s Halftime U.S.A. by The International Collegiates S1: 1. Stars and Stripes Forever 2. The Thunderer 3. The Washington Post 4. El Capitan 5. Semper Fidelis S2: 1. Yale Boola 2. Hands Across the Sea 3. The Victors 4. Manhattan Beach 5. Caissons 6. Marines Hymn
    - Around the World in Song, 1964 (Folder 72.11, Box 1822)
      American Children Sing Songs of Many Lands: “This Record presents children singing songs of many lands. These fresh and exuberant performances are by children of non-professional background who were coached for these recordings. Their ages range from eight to twelve years, and they exemplify the joy of participating and enjoying musical experiences together. Join them as they sing Around the World in Song.” [comes with booklet]
    - Victor, undated (Folder 72.12, Box 1822)
      Boris Godounow Symphonic Synthesis (Moussorgsky - arraigned: Stokowski) Leopold Stokoski and the Philadelphia Orchestra Parts 1 and 6 In Album Case
    - Victor, undated (Folder 72.13, Box 1822)
      Boris Godounow Symphonic Synthesis (Moussorgsky - arraigned: Stokowski) Leopold Stokoski and the Philadelphia Orchestra Parts 2 and 5 In Album Case
    - Victor, undated (Folder 72.14, Box 1822)
      Boris Godounow Symphonic Synthesis (Moussorgsky - arraigned: Stokowski) Leopold Stokoski and the Philadelphia Orchestra Parts 3 and 4 In Album Case
    - Herald, undated (Folder 74.01, Box 1822)
      Macy Associates presents Herald S1: Temptation (Brown-Freed-Berrios) Percy Faith and His Orchestra S2: Dancing in the Dark (Dietz-Schwartz) Percy Faith and His Orchestra
    - Victrola, undated (Folder 74.02, Box 1823)
      S1: Apres un reve (After a Dream) Pablo Casals S2: Chanson Villageoise (a Country Song) Pablo Casals
    - Courtney “Music You Feel”, undated (Folder 74.03, Box 1823)
      S1: Paradise Isle (Henry Kailinae) Kanaka Bush & His Hawaiians S2: Love Song of Tahiti (Dick McIntire) Kanaka Bush & His Hawaiians
    - Decca, undated (Folder 74. 04, Box 1823)
      S1: The Marines Hymn Fred Waring and his Pennsylvanians S2: Coast Guard Forever (Arthur Bryer) Fred Waring and his Pennsylvanians
    - Sahibinin Sesi, undated (Folder 74.05, Box 1823)
      S1: Yavas Yavas Bas da Gel Zehra Bilir S2: Deryalar Ostunde Gayig Degilum Zehra Bilir
    - Sahibinin Sesi, undated (Folder 74.06, Box 1823)
      S1: Gazel. Ey Siyah Goziu Kadin Nadir S2: Gazel. Gidelim Bahceye Nadir
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 74.07, Box 1823)
      Aloha Hawaii S1: Island Serenade Fox Trot-Vocal Chorus by Ensamble -Iona-Koki- Andy Iona and his Orchestra S2: Sweet Gardenia Lei Fox Trot - Vocal Chorus by Gary (Nalhe) Speare -McCann-Iona- Andy Iona and his Orchestra
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 74.08, Box 1823)
      Alametri Farika S1: Bir guzel kiz sahncakta Rluaseti Cumhur Orkestrasi S2: Istiklal Marsi Rluaseti Cumhur Orkestrasi
    - Pan-American, undated (Folder 74.09, Box 1823)
      Hawaiian Gems S1: Hawaiian War Chant Dan Kalauawa Stewart and His Islanders S2: Luau Hula Dan Kalauawa Stewart and His Islanders
    - Continental, undated (Folder 74.10, Box 1823)
      Electric Process Oriental S1: Tunisia (A. Maloof) Maloof Oriental Orchestra S2: Obelisque (A. Maloof) Maloof Oriental Orchestra
    - Standard International, undated (Folder 74.11, Box 1823)
      S1: By the Barn-Polka (B. Wyte) W. Bernard and his Orchestra S2: Oh Doctor!-Polka (B. Wyte) W. Bernard and his Orchestra
    - Capitol, undated (Folder 74.12, Box 1823)
      Arrangements by Julius Told S1: Blue Danube (Johann Strauss) S2: Southern Roses (Johann Strauss) Orchestra Conducted by Sam Freed
    - Sonora, undated (Folder 74.13, Box 1823)
      Ben Yost Singers S1: New York Songs: School Days East Side West Side The Bowery S2: Irish Songs: Sweet Rosie O’Grady Where did you Get that Hat And the Band Played On
    - Sahibinin Sesi, undated (Folder 74.14, Box 1823)
      S1: Ku[ripped]n Hicazkar Taksim. Ut Ile Udi Hrant S2: Huseyni Taksim. Ut ile Udi Hrant
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 74.15, Box 1823)
      Dinah Shore S1: How Soon (Will I Be Seeing You) -Owens-Lucas- S2: Fool That I Am -Hunt- Orchestra under the Direction of Sonny Burke
    - Scandinavia, undated (Folder 74.16, Box 1823)
      Selected Melodies from the North S1: Tantoli Svend Tollefsen’s Trio S2: Varsovienne Svend Tollefsen’s Trio
    - D.C.S.SR. Records, undated (Folder 74.17, Box 1823)
      American Revolution Bicentennial Roy Sutton S1: The Battle of Lexington (David C. Sutton, Sr.) S2: Freedom Bells
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 74.18, Box 1823)
      Frank Sinatra Orchestra under the direction of Axel Stordahl S1: Among My Souvenirs -Leslie-Nicholls- Vocal S2: September Song From “Knickerbocker Holiday” -Anderson-Weill- Vocal
    - Capitol, undated (Folder 74.19, Box 1823)
      Tex Ritter S1: I’m Gonna Leave You Like I Found You (Ritter-Dodd) S2: Long Time Gone
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 74.20, Box 1823)
      Benny Goodman and his Orchestra S1: A Gal in Calico Fox Trot- From “The Time, The Place And The Girl” Vocal Chorus by Eve Young -Robin-Schwartz- S2: Benjie’s Bubble Fox Trot -Goodman-Bushkin-
    - Victor, undated (Folder 74.21, Box 1823)
      George P. Watson S1: Emmett’s Favorite Yodel (J.K. Emmett) S2: Alpine Specialty - Popular Yodels
    - Capitol, undated (Folder 74.22, Box 1823)
      Stan Kenton and his Orchestra S1: Tampico (Fisher-Roberts) S2: Southern Scandal (Stan Kenton)
    - RCA Victor, undated (Folder 74.23, Box 1823)
      S1: The Glow-Worm (Lilla Cayley Robinson-Paul Lincke) (Arranged by Spike Jones) Spike Jones and his City Slickers Red Ingle and Aileen Carlisle with Chorus S2: Hawaiian War Chant (Ta-Hu-Wa-Hu-Wai) (Ralph Freed-Johnny Noble-Leleiohaku) Spike Jones and his Wacky Wakakians With chorus
    - Radiofunken, undated (Folder 74.24, Box 1823)
      Komponist Mit Orchester S1: Donaufreuden Walzer-Georg Freundorfer-Zithervirtuose S2: Fruehling in Berchtesgaden Walzer-Georg Freundorfer-Zithervirtuose
    - Victor Records, undated (Folder 74.25, Box 1823)
      S1: The Burglar Buck (Stephen O. Jones) Fred Van Eps Piano Accompaniment S2:Zallah - An Egyptian Intermezzo (Loraine) William H. Reitz With Orchestra
    - Telefunken, undated (Folder 74.26, Box 1823)
      Lajos Kiss Mit Orchester S1: Valse bleue (Alfred Margis) S2: Valse brune (Georges Krier)
    - Vocalion, undated (Folder 74.27, Box 1823)
      Cab Calloway and his Orchestra S1: Utt Da Zay (The Tailor’s Song) -Ram-Mills- S2: Crescendo in Drums -Cole-Hart-Battle-Smith- Featuring Cozy Cole
    - Victor, undated (Folder 74.28, Box 1823)
      Glenn Miller and his Orchestra S1: (I’ve Got a Gal in) Kalamazoo - Fox Trot (from “Orchestra Wives”) Vocal refrain by Tex Beneke Marion Hutton and The Modernaires S2: At Last - Fox Trot ( from “Orchestra Wives” -Mack Gordon-Harry Warren) Vocal refrain by Ray Eberle
    - The Dartmouth Glee Club, undated (Folder 74.29, Box 1823)
      “Dartmouth in Song” S1: Men of Dartmouth Richard Hovey, ’85 & Harry Wallman, ‘07 S2: The Hanover Winter Song Richard Hovey, ‘85
    - Capitol, undated (Folder 74.30, Box 1823)
      Paul Weston and his Orchestra with Margaret Whiting S1: How Deep is the Ocean (Irving Berlin) S2: It Might as Well be Spring (Rodgers-Hammerstein II)
    - Victor, undated (Folder 74.31, Box 1823)
      Tommy Dorsey and his Orchestra, vocal refrain by Frank Sinatra S1: Love Me As I Am - Fox Trot (from “Caught in the Draft”) (Frank Loesser-Louis Alter) S2:Nine Old Men - Fox Trot (Los Nueve Viejos) (Tom Adair-Matt Dannis)
    - Victor, undated (Folder 74.32, Box 1823)
      Pietro S1: Over the Waves Waltz (Sobre las Olas) (Rosas) S2: Sirens Waltz (Sirene) (Waldteufel)
    - MGM, undated (Folder 74.33, Box 1823)
      Bert Shefter and his String Octet S1: Fiddle-Faddle (Anderson) S2: Jazz Pizzicato and Jazz Legato (Anderson)
    - ARA, undated (Folder 74.34, Box 1823)
      Hoagy Carmichael & Orchestra S1: How Little We Know (Carmichael-Mercer) Vocal by Anita Boyer S2: Hong Kong Blues (Carmichael) Vocal by Hoagy Carmichael
    - Decca, undated (Folder 74.35, Box 1823)
      Ted Fido Rico and his Orchestra S1: My Little Glass Shack in Kealakekua, Hawaii (Bill Cogswell-Tommy Harrison-Johnny Nobel) S1: King Kamehameha (Ted Rio Rito-Johnny Nobel)
    - Victor, undated (Folder 74.36, Box 1823)
      Master Yodeler, Fred Mueller with guitar Zithers by Engl and Riedl S1: Bayrisch Zell (Yodel and Arr. By F. Mueller) S2: Lousach Tal (Yodel and Arr. By F. Mueller)
    - Bluebird, undated (Folder 74.37, Box 1823)
      Charles Kama and his Moana Hawaiians with Vocal Refrain S1: When My Ship Sails Away From Hawaii - Waltz (Charles Kama - Yvonne Reanau) S2: Blue Moon Over the Islands - F.T. (Charles Kame - Yvonne Reanau)
    - Victor, undated (Folder 74.38, Box 1823)
      Jimmie Rodgers, Singing with Guitar S1: Blue Yodel No. 6 (Jimmie Rodgers) S2: Yodeling Cowboy (Jimmie Rodgers -Elsie MacWilliams)
    - Capitol, undated (Folder 74.39, Box 1823)
      S1: Nature Boy (Eden Ahbez) King Cole With Orchestra conducted by Frank De Vol S2: Lost April (De Lange-Newman-Spencer) From “The Bishop’s Wife” The King Cole Trio With Orchestra Conducted by Carlyle Hall
    - Decca, undated (Folder 74.40, Box 1823)
      Dick Hayes and The Song Spinners S1: In My Arms (Ted Grouya-Frank Loesser) S2: It Can’t Be Wrong (from “Now Voyager”) (Max Steiner-Kim Gannon)
    - Victor, undated (Folder 75.01, Box 1824)
      S1: Ensueno-Son (Al D’Arteaga-Pedro Telleria-Bob Steinberg) Panchito and his La Conga Orchestra S2: Pepita-Conga (Eliseo Grenet) Panchito and his La Conga Orchestra
    - Standard, undated (Folder 75.02, Box 1824)
      Viola Turpeinen’s Scandinavian Ensemble S1: Tanneri-Waltz S2: Harlem-Schottis
    - Nordic, undated (Folder 75.03, Box 1824)
      The Northernaires Quartet S1: Je, vi elsker dette landet (Bjornson, Nordraak) S2: Gud signe Norrigs land (Arne Garborg)
    - Victor, undated (Folder 75.04, Box 1824)
      Victor Orchestra S1: Quadrille-Figure 3 1. Captain Jinks 2. Rosin the Bow S2: Sicilian Circle 1.Uncle Steve 2. Mrs. Monroe’s Jig 3. We’re On the Road to Boston
    - Decca, undated (Folder 75.05, Box 1824)
      From Theater Guild Musical Play “Oklahoma” S1: I Cain’t Say No (Act 1 - Scene 1) (Richard Rodgers - Oscar Hammerstein II) Celeste Holm with Oklahoma Orchestra, under direction of Jay Blackton S2: Pore Jud is Daid (Act 1 - Scene 2) (Richard Rodgers - Oscar Hammerstein II) Alfred Drake and Howard da Silva with Oklahoma Orchestra, under direction of Jay Blackton
    - Decca, undated (Folder 75.06, Box 1824)
      From Rodgers-Hammerstein II Production “Annie Get Your Gun” S1: You Can’t Get a Man With a Gun (Irving Berlin) Ethel Merman with Anne Get Your Gun Orchestra, under direction of Jay Blackton S2: I’m An Indian Too (Irving Berlin) Ethel Merman with Anne Get Your Gun Orchestra, under direction of Jay Blackton
    - Decca, undated (Folder 75.07, Box 1824)
      Al Kealoha Perry and His Singing Surfriders S1: Ta-Hu-Wa-Hu-Wai (Hawaiian War Chant) S2: Kalakaua (Ancient King)
    - CBS Sound Effects, undated (Folder 75.08, Box 1824)
      S1: 32 Cal. Automatic Pistol (Seven Cuts - 1-2-3-4-5-6-8 Shots) S2: 16 Ga. Shotgun A-One Shot B-Two Shots 12 Ga. Shotgun C-One Shot D-Two Shots E-Five Shots
    - Columbia, undated (Folder 75.09, Box 1824)